<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My First App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="myauto">        Ferguson says that he saw Manchester United "change from a conventional football club to what is now a major business enterprise and he never failed to move with the times." He says that it was nothing other than his "man-management" skills that helped him to deal with the global stars. His relationship with Cristiano Ronaldo has got special importance in the book.[1] He says that he never wanted Ronaldo to join Real Madrid.[2] In this book, he also expresses his feelings about players such as David Beckham and Ryan Giggs.[3]</string>


    <string-array name="desc">

        <item>Having learned the basic moves, how exactly should a player improve? In this popular classic, the author explains 33 complete games, in detail, move by move, including the reason for each one. Playing through these games and explanations gives real insight into the power of the pieces and how to post them most effectively. "The novice who plays through Logical Chess can learn an ocean of basic chess wisdom."—Leonard Barden, Engilsh chess master and broadcaster “Entertains . . . as it reinforces strategic lessons gleaned from chess titans. Illustrates effective middle-game plans.”—Library Journal</item>
        Ferguson says that he saw Manchester United "change from a conventional football club to what is now a major business enterprise and he never failed to move with the times." He says that it was nothing other than his "man-management" skills that helped him to deal with the global stars. His relationship with Cristiano Ronaldo has got special importance in the book.[1] He says that he never wanted Ronaldo to join Real Madrid.[2] In this book, he also expresses his feelings about players such as David Beckham and Ryan Giggs.[3]
        <item>For the very first time, world-renowned and revolutionary football manager Arsène Wenger tells his own story. He opens up about his life, sharing principles for success on and off the field with lessons on leadership, and vivid tales of his 22 years managing Arsenal to unprecedented success.In My Life in Red and White, Wenger charts his extraordinary career, including his rise in France and Japan where he managed Nancy, Monaco and Nagoya Grampus Eight (clubs that also play in red-and-white, like Arsenal!) to his 22 years at the helm of an internationally renowned club from 1996 onwards. He describes the unrest that led to his resignation in 2018, and his current role as Chief of Global Football Development for FIFA.</item>
        <item>I Heard You Paint Houses: Frank "The Irishman" Sheeran and Closing the Case on Jimmy Hoffa is a 2004 work of narrative nonfiction written by former homicide prosecutor, investigator and defense attorney Charles Brandt that chronicles the life of Frank Sheeran, an alleged mafia hitman who confesses the crimes he committed working for the Bufalino crime family.</item>
        <item>In the stirring, highly anticipated first volume of his presidential memoirs, Barack Obama tells the story of his improbable odyssey from young man searching for his identity to leader of the free world, describing in strikingly personal detail both his political education and the landmark moments of the first term of his historic presidency—a time of dramatic transformation and turmoil.Obama takes readers on a compelling journey from his earliest political aspirations to the pivotal Iowa caucus victory that demonstrated the power of grassroots activism to the watershed night of November 4, 2008, when he was elected 44th president of the United States</item>
        <item>Revised, updated, and expanded, this practical hands-on book is packed full of step-by-step guidelines and suggestions for carrying out a multitude of leadership tasks and responsibilities focused on  a changing work force that serves an equally changing and complex society. While emphasizing the real value of common sense in good leadership practices, the author furnishes the aspiring novice or veteran police supervisor with specific advice on how to train, counsel, inspect, discipline, and assess the performance of his or her subordinates. He strives to help the supervisor with the vital obligations of being a planner</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>
